Suffrage Collection, 1851-2009 (bulk 1880s-1920s)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- BOOKS ON SHELF
  - Blackwell, Alice Stone, Lucy Stone: Pioneer of Woman's Rights 1930 (autographed copy)
  - Brown, Gertrude Foster, Suffrage and Music: My First Eighty Years 1978
  - Brown, Mrs. Raymond (Gertrude Foster Brown), Your Vote, and How to Use It 1918
  - Bushnell, Horace, Women's Suffrage; the Reform Against Nature 1869
  - Crothers, Samuel M., Meditations on Votes for Women 1914
  - Franklin, Margaret Ladd, The Case for Woman Suffrage: A Bibliography 1913
  - International Woman Suffrage Alliance, Woman suffrage in practice, 1913
  - Johnson, Helen Kendrick, Woman and the Republic 1909
  - Kaplan, Judith, Woman Suffrage1977
  - Kleber, Mrs. L.O, Suffrage Cookbook 1915
  - Mackenzie, Midge, Shoulder to Shoulder 1975
  - Miller, Alice Duer, Are Women People? 1915
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA), Proceedings 1893-99
  - -, Handbook 1900-08
  - -, Handbook 1909-14
  - -, Handbook 1915-20
  - -, Victory: How Women Won It, 1840-19401940
  - -, Woman Suffrage: Arguments and Resultsundated
  - Putman-Jacobi, Mary, "Common Sense" Applied to Woman Suffrage 1894
  - Sumner, Helen L., Equal Suffrage 1909
  - The Suffrage Annual and Women's Who's Who (London)1913
  - Women's Suffrage (bound pamphlets)
  - Women's Suffrage: Quotation Bookundated
  - Wright, Sir Almoth E., The Unexpurgated Case Against Woman's Suffrage 1913
- MICROFORMS (Media Center)
  - Woman's Journal, volumes 1-47 (M23) (Box MF)
  - Mary Bartlett Dixon Cullen: scrapbooks (15 volumes) 1909-20 (M24) (Box MF)
  - Jus Suffragii 1906-14 (M29), [continued as International Women's Suffrage News and International Women's News, in Periodicals Collection] (Box MF)
  - National Union of Women's Suffrage Societies: Women's Suffrage Pilgrimage Journal 1913 (M34) (Box MF)